Here comes revenge.
Hounds of War is a action, thriller film directed by Isaac Florentine.
After a mission goes wrong, only one of a group of mercenaries
is left alive to avenge his fallen brothers.
Ryder, played by Frank Grillo.
Colonel Hart, played by Robert Patrick.
Selina, played by Rhona Mitra.
Bulldog, played by Leeshon Alexander.
Hollywood, played by Urs Rechn.
President Lane, played by Matthew Marsh.
Hounds of War is a 2024 American action thriller film directed by
Isaac Florentine and written by Jean-Pierre Magro.
It stars Frank Grillo, Robert Patrick, and Rhona Mitra in leading roles.
The film explores themes of revenge, betrayal, and
survival against military warfare.
It was released on September 20, 2024, by XYZ Films.
The tone is intense.